Malden, Mass. First Church records, 1649-2016.
Congregational Library & Archives
- Church records, 1767 2016; 1767-2016
  - Property records, 1833 1964; 1833-1964
    This subseries contains records relating to the church's building and property including deeds, pew deeds and plans, correspondence, building plans, reports, contracts, and renovation and maintainace records.
    - Pew Deeds, 1833 1856; 1833-1856 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Property and Legal Records, 1860 1964; 1860-1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Pew Deeds, 1871 1874; 1871-1874 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Pew Holders, Deeds, and Valuation, 1871 1913; 1871-1913 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Plans and Diagrams, 1871 1976; 1871-1976 (Folder 4)
    - Building Committee and Property Records, 1892 1919; 1892-1919 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Pew Dues, 1910 1917; 1910-1917 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Floor Plans, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Parish House and Church Extension Records, 1921 1924; 1921-1924 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Parish House Construction and Dedication, 1922 1923; 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Pew Rental Discontinuation, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Collens, and Willis Architects, 1933 1934; 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Architect Selection Correspondence, 1933 1934; 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Building Contracts and Orders, 1934 1935; 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Property and Maintenance Records, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Termite Control, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Parish House Renovation, 1958 1960; 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Historical Display Materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Innkeeper's Daughter" Pageant, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Tenebrae Service and Readings, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Women of the Bible" Pageant, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Doctrine, Articles of Faith, and Covenant, 1823 1896; 1823-1896 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Certificates, 1850 1974; 1850-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Notification Letters, 1857 1869; 1857-1869 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Events, 1869 1994; 1869-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Records and Correspondence, 1869 2005; 1869-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Reports, and News Scrapbook, 1888 1905; 1888-1905 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - List of Records Deposited at Malden Public Library, 1888 1908; 1888-1908 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 250th Anniversary, 1898 1899; 1898-1899 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Communion Silver on Loan at MFA, 1908 1949; 1908-1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Member Correspondence, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Information Cards, 1914 1923; 1914-1923 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1914 1926; 1914-1926 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Malden Religious Education, 1916 1917; 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Book of Remembrance Memorials, 1916 1995; 1916-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Attendence Record, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Reports, Correspondence, and Member Records, 1922 1931; 1922-1931 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 275th Anniversary, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ballots and Pastoral Supply Committee, 1925 1969; 1925-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Congregational Year Books, 1926 1963; 1926-1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - British Congregational Pilgrimage, 1928 1934; 1928-1934 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Publicity, 1928 1980; 1928-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hymnals, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Member Correspondence, 1930 1945; 1930-1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Posters and Memorials, 1960 1960; 1930-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Programs and Attendance, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Fire Aftermath Meeting and Correspondence, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fire Publicity, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1933 1936; 1933-1936 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Organ Bids and Correspondence, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Builders' Service, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Preaching Mission, 1935 1936; 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Publicity, 1935 1962; 1935-1962 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - By-Laws, 1940 1998; 1940-1998 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gospel Team Corrrespondence, 1943 1944; 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dictaphone Wartime Relocation Certificates, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Copy of Women's Petition to Keep Minister, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Historic Malden Newspaper Scrapbook, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Tercentenary Anniversary, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Tercentenary Book of Remembrance, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Tercentenary Pageants, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Tercentenary Publicity, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Tercentenary Scrapbook, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Tercentenary Scrapbook Presented by Louise Wallingford, 1949 1957; 1949-1957 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Church Histories, 1949 1977; 1949-1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Carillon Instructions and Diagrams, 1954 1958; 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Records Entrusted to Malden Bank, 1956 1957; 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Violin Purchase and Certification, 1957 1959; 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Piano, 1960 1962; 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Woburn Association, 1961 1962; 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, 1965 1968; 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Copies of Plaques, 1967 1971; 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Church Outings, 1970 1973; 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - The Heritage Apartments Ceremonies, 1971 1972; 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - The Heritage Apartments Publicity, 1971 1972; 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 325th Anniversary, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 325th Anniversary Scrapbook, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Congregational Way, 1974 1975; 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Bicentennial Celebrations, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Memorials, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 330th Anniversary, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Thanksgiving Pageant, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - YWCA, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Advertisements, 1991 1998; 1991-1998 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bible Outline, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - American Guild of Organists, 1997 2000; 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 350th Anniversary Coloring Book, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Parsonage Gatherings, 2000 2001; 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Community Engagement Publicity, 2001 2003; 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Flower Orders, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Church organizations, 1830 2014; 1830-2014
  This series contains records from various groups, committees, and societies at First Church in Malden includinng minutes, reports, account books, correspondence, certificates, programs and scripts, and other related documents.
  - Auxiliary groups, 1897 2009; 1897-2009
    This subseries contains records from various clubs and groups and includes programs, scripts, certificates, reports, minutes, flyers, and other related documents.
    - Men's Club, 1897 1970; 1897-1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Drama Club Plays, 1921 1949; 1921-1949 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Drama Club, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Boy Scouts, 1924 1977; 1924-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Men's Club Flyers and Correspondence, 1928 1953; 1928-1953 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Beacon Class Minutes, 1930 1936; 1930-1936 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Junior Choir Program and Payroll, 1931 1932; 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Youth Fellowship, 1934 1972; 1934-1972 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - 7:30 Club Newstories and Reunion, 1938 1982; 1938-1982 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Youth Groups, 1960 1988; 1960-1988 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Youth Fellowship Trips, 2002 2009; 2002-2009 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Church committee, 1889 1936; 1889-1936
    This subseries contains records from the church committee including minutes, reports, and correspondence.
    - Church Committee Minutes, 1889 1897; 1889-1897 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Church Committee Minutes, 1898 1906; 1898-1906 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Church Committee Minutes, 1906 1914; 1906-1914 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Church Committee Minutes, 1915 1936; 1915-1936 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Church Committee Records, 1928 1931; 1928-1931 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Council, 1931 2014; 1931-2014
    This subseries contains records related to the church council including minutes, correspondence, and reports.
    - Church Council Minutes and Correspondence, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Council Minutes, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Council Minutes, 1939 1940; 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Council Minutes, 1958 1976; 1958-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Council Minutes, 1991 1996; 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Council Minutes and Reports, 1997 2001; 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Council Minutes and Reports, 2002 2003; 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Council Minutes and Reports, 2004 2005; 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Council Minutes and Records, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Council Minutes and Reports, 2007 2014; 2007-2014 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Prudential committee, 1926 1996; 1926-1996
    This subseries contains records from the prudential committee including minutes, correspondence, reports, and other related documents.
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1926 1931; 1926-1931 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Prudential Committee Correspondence and Records, 1926 1961; 1926-1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1927 1928; 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1930 1932; 1930-1932 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1934 1935; 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Prudential Committee Minutes, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1936 1937; 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1936 1937; 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Prudential Committee Minutes and Records, 1938 1939; 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Prudential Committee Minutes and Records, 1939 1940; 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Prudential Committee Records, 1965 1996; 1965-1996 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Prudential Committee Minutes, 1977 1979; 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Religious Education, 1926 2002; 1926-2002
    This subseries contains records from the religious education committee, also known as the christian education committee, including minutes, reports, and correspondence.
    - Religious Education Minutes and Correspondence, 1926 1937; 1926-1937 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Religious Education Minutes and Records, 1931 1947; 1931-1947 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Christian Education Minutes, 1964 1975; 1964-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Christian Education Minutes and Records, 1992 1996; 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Christian Education Minutes and Records, 1999 2002; 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Trinitarian Congregational Society, 1830 1920; 1830-1920
    This subseries contains records from the Trinitarian Congregational Society which began in 1832 and ended in 1920 and included at times a standing committee and building committee. The records include minutes, account books, by-laws, member lists, and record volumes.
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Minutes and Constitutions, 1830 1850; 1830-1850 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Minutes, 1850 1876; 1850-1876 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Treasurer's Account Book, 1858 1909; 1858-1909 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Standing Committee Minutes, 1864 1881; 1864-1881 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Building Committee Records, 1869 1883; 1869-1883 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society By-Laws, 1871 1914; 1871-1914 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society By-Laws and Member List, 1874 1920; 1874-1920 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Minutes, 1877 1920; 1877-1920 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Standing Committee Minutes, 1882 1895; 1882-1895 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Trinitarian Congregational Society Treasurer's Account Book, 1909 1920; 1909-1920 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, 1930 1993; 1930-1993
    This subseries contains records from the trustees including annual reports, financial reports, minutes, and correspondence.
    - Trustees Fund Reports and Correspondence, 1930 1990; 1930-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Trustees Annual Report, 1935 1936; 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Trustees Reports, 1945 1978; 1945-1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Trustees Minutes, 1952 1993; 1952-1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Committee Financial Records, 1818 1825; 1818-1825 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Joint and Prudential Committee Minutes, 1931 1932; 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee Pledge Correspondence, 1931 1957; 1931-1957 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Joint Committee and Council Minutes, 1932 1933; 1932-1933 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Building Committee Construction Correspondence, 1933 1935; 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Building Committee Minutes, 1933 1935; 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tercentenary Committee Correspondence, 1948 1949; 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee, 1956 1957; 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Survey Committee, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Building Committee, 1958 1960; 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bus and Transportation Committee, 1965 1975; 1965-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Duties of a Deacon, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Leadership Committee, 1969 1979; 1969-1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Finance Committee, 1975 1978; 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Pulpit Supply Committee Profile and Manual, 1984 1988; 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Diaconate Records and Correspondence, 1986 1995; 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Diaconate Minutes, 1987 2002; 1987-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Committee Records, 1993 2009; 1993-2009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Property Management and Prudential Committee Minutes and Reports, 1955 1999; 1995-1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Organization Directories and Records, 1997 2011; 1997-2011 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Committee Minutes and Reports, 1999 2011; 1999-2011 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Missions Committee Minutes and Reports, 1999 2011; 1999-2011 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Property Management and Prudential Committee Minutes, 1999 2011; 1999-2011 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Stewardship Minutes and Campaigns, 2007 2008; 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Clerk's Committee and Council Records, 1941 1944; 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Women's guild, 1832 1989; 1832-1989
  This series contains records from the various women's groups at First Church beginning with the Ladies Benevolent Society in 1832 which became part of the Women's League established in 1913 before it merged with the Congregational Guild, formed in 1926, to become the Women's Guild in 1929. The records contain minutes, reports, correspondence, scrapbooks, calendar booklets, histories, news stories, guides and orders, photos, account books, songs, and other documents.
  - Women's circles, 1924 1989; 1924-1989
    This subseries contains records from various circles, which were smaller groups within the congregational guild, women's league, and women's guild, including minutes, reports, scrapbooks, histories, correspondence, account books, member lists, and volumes.
    - Circle 1 Account Book, 1937 1941; 1937-1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Circle 1 Minutes, 1937 1941; 1937-1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Circle A Account Book, 1936 1976; 1936-1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Circle A Minutes, 1936 1945; 1936-1945 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Circle A Minutes, 1945 1958; 1945-1958 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Circle A Minutes, 1958 1968; 1958-1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Circle A Minutes, 1971 1982; 1971-1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Circle A Minutes and Correspondence, 1983 1989; 1983-1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Circle M Minutes, 1931 1949; 1931-1949 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Circle M Scrapbook, 1939 1940; 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Circle M Minutes, 1949 1976; 1949-1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Circle M History, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Circle R Minutes, 1929 1942; 1929-1942 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Circle R Minutes, 1936 1952; 1936-1952 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Circle R Minutes, 1952 1958; 1952-1958 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Circle R Correspondence, Reports, and Member Booklets, 1953 1979; 1953-1979 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Circle R Minutes, 1959 1972; 1959-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Circle R Meeting Notes, 1968 1972; 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Circle R Minutes, 1972 1983; 1972-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Circle R Meeting Notes, 1973 1982; 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Circle S Minutes, 1935 1951; 1935-1951 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Circle S Minutes, 1951 1964; 1951-1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Circle W Minutes, 1924 1939; 1924-1939 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Circle W Minutes, 1939 1949; 1939-1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Circle W Minutes, 1949 1960; 1949-1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Circle W Minutes, 1960 1975; 1960-1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Women's Guild Songs, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ladies Benevolent Society Minutes and Annual Reports, 1832 1881; 1832-1881 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ladies Benevolent Society Minutes and Annual Reports, 1882 1908; 1882-1908 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ladies Benevolent Society Constitution and Calendars, 1893 1908; 1893-1908 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Mother's Association, 1898 1906; 1898-1906 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1902 1978; 1902-1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ladies Benevolent Society Minutes and Annual Reports, 1909 1940; 1909-1940 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Women's League and Congregational Guild Calendars, 1914 1926; 1914-1926 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Congregational Guild Minutes, 1916 1923; 1916-1923 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Women's League Reports and Photos, 1923 1926; 1923-1926 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Congregational Guild Minutes, 1924 1929; 1924-1929 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Women's Guild Minutes, 1929 1940; 1929-1940 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1929 1948; 1929-1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Social Committee Events and Reports, 1931 1940; 1931-1940 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Women's Guild Calendars, 1932 1958; 1932-1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Social Committee Events and Reports, 1940 1944; 1940-1944 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - News Reports, 1946 1947; 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Histories, 1949 1973; 1949-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Women's Guild Minutes, 1951 1966; 1951-1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Annual and Financial Reports, 1954 1965; 1954-1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1955 1961; 1955-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hand Bells, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stewardship Guide and Dedications, 1956 1968; 1956-1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Women's Guild Funds and Events Account Book, 1958 1972; 1958-1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Women's Guild Notes and Guidelines, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Women's Guild Calendars, 1959 1973; 1959-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1961 1968; 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Orders of Installation, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Lobster Luncheon Reports, 1965 1972; 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Annual and Financial Reports, 1965 1985; 1965-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Women's Guild Minutes, 1966 1986; 1966-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1968 1970; 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Women's Guild Account Book, 1969 1970; 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Women's Guild Account Book, 1970 1971; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Mother's Club Minutes, 1970 1976; 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial Correspondence and Reports, 1971 1972; 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Women's Guild Account Book, 1971 1972; 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Friendly Service, 1971 1982; 1971-1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Missionary and Outreach Work, 1979 1982; 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Member records, 1804 2008; 1804-2008
  This series contains vital statistics and records about the church members including marriage information, registers, guest books, member cards, member lists, directories, transfer booklets, obituaries, mailing lists, and manuals with member lists.
  - Directories, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Register, 1804 1999; 1804-1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Register, 1832 1969; 1832-1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Original Member Cards, 1833 1883; 1833-1883 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Manuals and Member Lists, 1859 1889; 1859-1889 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Manual and Member List, 1889 1891; 1889-1891 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Letters of Dismission Book, 1897 1900; 1897-1900 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Directory Booklets, 1900 1922; 1900-1922 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Communion Services and Member Additions, 1915 1919; 1915-1919 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Member Register, 1915 1957; 1915-1957 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Officer List, 1920 1939; 1920-1939 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Obituaries, 1923 1974; 1923-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Member Due Cards, 1931 1940; 1931-1940 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Member List, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Member List, 1936 1938; 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Membership Record List, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Committee and Officer Directories, 1958 1999; 1958-1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Letters of Dismission Booklets, 1959 1968; 1959-1968 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Membership Certificates, 1961 1969; 1961-1969 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Membership Transfer Booklets, 1969 1982; 1969-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mailing List, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 1982 1987; 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Directory Booklets, 1982 1996; 1982-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Marriage Information Envelopes, 1993 1996; 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Guest Log, 1994 2000; 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Marriage Information Envelopes, 1997 2003; 1997-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Directory Booklets, 1998 2008; 1998-2008 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Publications, 1848 2013; 1848-2013
  This series contains records published by or about the church including their newsletter known as "The Cornerstone", service programs, published histories, brochures, and calendars.
  - Church Introduction, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Church Newspaper, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1958 1962; 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1963 1966; 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1967 1970; 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1971 1974; 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1975 1979; 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1980 1983; 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1984 1986; 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1987 1989; 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1990 1992; 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1993 1995; 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1996 1998; 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "The Cornerstone", 1999 2000; 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "The Cornerstone", 2001 2002; 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "The Cornerstone", 2003 2005; 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "The Cornerstone", 2006 2008; 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "The Cornerstone", 2009 2011; 2009-2011 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Dedications, 1923 1968; 1923-1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "The Ecclesiastical History of Malden" Excerpt, 1890 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Flyers and Announcements, 1992 2006; 1992-2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Guide and Instruction Booklets, 1934 1975; 1934-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Installations, 1848 1960; 1848-1960 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Letters and Bulletins, 1960 1995; 1960-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Malden from Primitive Past to Progressive Present" Manuscript, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Malden Official Souvenir Program, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Meeting House Bulletin, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Official Tercentenary Guide, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ordination Services, 1962 1967; 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Parish Letters, 1925 1952; 1925-1952 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pastor Letters, 1996 2011; 1996-2011 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Programs, 1897 1929; 1897-1929 (Box 11, Folder 20)